

Personal details

Singaram Sahithya Reddy sahithyaareddy6@gmail.com

09642792666

Madhura Nagar, Hyderabad-500038 Telangana

October 17th, 2002

O⊃ Female

inkedin.com/in/sahithyareddy-17a2122

Skills

Microsoft Word Microsoft Powerpoint

....

Tableau Application Oracle SOL

Orange Hobbies

Microsoft Excel

Event Organizing

Swimming ■ Dance

■ Art

■ Yona

Singaram Sahithya Reddy

Objective

I am a determined and hard-working candidate, working toward developing more skill sets and qualities to acquire a position in a company that helps me grow and develop further ahead in the field of business management and analytics. Resourceful team player with experience with common software applications and social media platforms. Well-versed in business organization and strategies for successfully modernizing workplaces. Skilled at project sunnert with a proven history of solutions oriented problem-solving

Education

Work History

Matriculate Dinloma Jul 2008 - Mar 2018 Hyderabad Public School, Hyderabad

High School Diploma Jun 2018 - Apr 2020 St. Mary's Junior College, Hyderabad

BBA: Business Analytics Jun 2020 - Present Christ University, Lavasa-Pune

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Little Master, Hyderabad Academic Project Jul 2021 - Aug 2021 Industry Review Project, Hyderabad

Achievements

· 1st price in filmkari of Anuncio-2018 Participated in The Ducibus -The Best Management Team event of IGNITE 2022

· Runner up in Ahaan event Volunteered in Imperio 2022

Certificates

2020 Investment Banking and Global Markets-Moodys

Applied Excel- Moodys 2021 R- Programming 2021

Google Digital Marketing 2021

Languages

Extracurricular activities

English

Hindi

Telugu Tamil Played Hockey and volleyball for extramurals competition

Worked as a volunteer in ashray akruti (NGO)

Volunteer in Stage and event team of SWO (Social Welfare Organization)

Volunteer for Imperio 2021-2022 CUSBMA

Member at CU IEEE

Member at CSA

Member of CU CEBT

SEMINAR AND WORKSHOPS ATTENDED

- FinTech: The growth of fintech in emerging economies: A case study of India and Nigeria. - Mar 2022
- Integrated approach in science and technology for a sustainable future.
 Feb 2022
 - Importance of IPR- Feb 2022
 Participated in TEDxChristULavasa held on 29th May, 2021